Shakir SULTANOV



WEB DEVELOPER | POWERCODERS PARTICIPANT

PROFILE

I am a diligent and ambitious individual with a positive outlook and a relentless drive for continuous learning and professional growth. Throughout my academic and self-learning journey, I have had the opportunity to explore diverse areas of IT. I am dedicated to further expanding my experience and skills to become a highly proficient and successful developer.

CONTACT

Ukrainian, S Permit



shakir.sultanov@powercoders.org



+41 76 454 7413



Schützenstrasse 11, 8636 Wald ZH



LANGUAGES

Mother Tongue Russian Ukrainian **Mother Tongue** Turkish **Mother Tongue**

English German Α1

REFERENCES

Geges LÖWL

Company Relations Manager, Powercoders geges.loewl@powercoders.org

+41 77 469 15 86

HOBBIES

Read

I love reading psychological books, books to understand life, people, and the world.

Music

Love to listen to music when I working on something, especially violin.

IT SKILLS

Intermediate JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Beginner

Basic PostgreSQL, C#, Java, Android Studio, Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

11.2022 - Present

Frontender, Part-time Freelance, Odesa, Ukraine

Responsible for design and frontend development

02.2018 - 01.2021

Seller-loader, LLC "Manufactured goods market", Odesa, Ukraine

- Responsible for loading
- Organize warehouse inventory efficiently
- Responsibly fulfill customer orders

EDUCATION

09.2018 - 07.2022

Bachelor of Computer Engineering - Odesa Mechnikov National University, Odesa, Ukraine

- Programming fundamentals
- Computer Engineering fundamentals
- Data structures and algorithms
- Computer networks
- Operating systems
- Web and mobile development

10.2022 - 01.2023

freeCodeCamp - Web certification, Odesa, Ukraine

HTML, CSS

CONTINUOUS EDUCATION

04.2024 - Present

Powercoders Bootcamp - ICT Work Integration Program, Bern

- Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Weekly business & social skills training (teamwork, communication, etc.)

01.2024 - Present

The Complete 2024 Web Development Bootcamp (Online) -Udemy, Zürich

HTML, CSS, JS, React, Databases, Git, etc.